（忆往昔）
路西法没了
Lucifer is gone.
- 去哪了 - 我不知道
- To where? - I don't know.
路西法逃跑是因为他虚弱不堪
Lucifer's running because he's weak.
地狱绝不会追随你
Hell will never follow you.
你给了我我最需要的
You gave me what I needed most.
我想给予你同样的回报
I want to do the same for you.
妈妈
Mom?
我是图妮·贝维尔 记录者 伦敦分会的
Toni Bevell. Men of Letters, London Chapterhouse.
- 迪恩呢 - 死了
- Where's Dean? - Dead.
把枪放下
Put the gun down.
我需要你告诉我名字 地址
I need you to give me names and locations.
和其他一切
and everything else.
去 你 妈
Screw…you.
你真要逼我这么做吗
Are you really gonna make me do this?
常言说得好
You know what they say.
好事都…
Good things come to those …
谢谢 妈妈
Thanks, Mom.
不再尝试击垮他的身体 而是击垮他的头脑
Stop trying to break his body. We break his mind.
或许你并不那么擅长你的工作
Maybe you're not as good at your job as you think.
不
No!
（如今）
这样不是好多了吗 萨姆
Isn't this much more pleasant, Sam?
我得说 这我可没想到
I got to say, I did not see that happening.
常言说得好
Well, you know what they say.
异性相吸
Opposites attract.
我们会到那一步的 萨姆
Oh, we'll get there, Sam.
再问几个问题
Just another couple of questions.
[邪恶力量 第12季第2集]
有意思
Fascinating.
但你肯定在夸大吧
But surely you exaggerate.
美国猎人不可能像你说的那么糟
American Hunters can't be as bad as you say.
嗯 真就那么糟
Yeah. Uh, yeah, they can.
怎么 英国不是这样吗
What, they're not in the U.K.?
不
No.
他们为我们工作
No, they work for us.
是工具 只杀 不思考
Tools. They kill. They don't think.
是谁招募了你和你哥哥
Who recruited you and your brother?
你们向谁报告
To whom do you report?
我们
We, uh…
我们不会只说一晚的话吧
We're not just gonna talk all night, right?
我在监控上没有任何发现
I haven't found anything on these surveillance cameras.
他们就像凭空消失了
I mean, it's like they just disappeared.
你呢 有没有当地的片警
How about you? Any of the local beat cops.
看到什么形迹可疑的人
see anybody that shouldn't be there?
这里挺偏僻 没几个片警
It's pretty rural. Not a lot of beat cops.
我查过了所有旅馆 废弃建筑
I've checked all the motels, abandoned buildings.
没有萨姆的踪迹
No sign of Sam.
好吧
All right.
我说不好 去地产中介办公室转转
I don't know. You know, check… real-estate offices.
看有没有人买下或租了什么地方
See if anybody bought a place or rented a place.
这些人连飞机都有
I mean, these people had a freakin' plane.
或许他们都走正规途径
Maybe they do things legit.
好 明白了
Okay, I understand.
明早打给你
I'll call you in the morning.
小卡
Cass, hey.
是这样
So, here's the thing.
妈妈回来后
It's been kind of weird here.
感觉怪怪的
with, you know, Mom being back.
我们似乎不知道该如何跟彼此相处
It's like we don't know how to act around each other,
所以我们就拉拉家常 装作一切正常
so we just kind of make this small talk and act normal,
但绝对不正常的
but it's … it's so not normal.
我也说不好
Um, I'm … I'm not sure.
她对你说了什么
What … what has she said to you?
没说什么
Well, nothing.
问题就在这里
That … that … that's the whole point.
你对她说了什么
Okay, what have you said to her?
也没什么
Well, nothing. I'm …
我不知道该对她说什么
I don't know what to say to her, you know?
这一切让人太难接受
It … it's … it's like it's all just too much,
我不想让她承受不来
and…I don't want to overwhelm her.
别没必要地把事情复杂化了
Don't make things needlessly complicated,
你们人类总这样
as you humans tend to do.
我再打给你
I'll call you.
嗯 好
Yeah. Great.
真有帮助 多谢了
That's helpful. Thanks.
有萨姆的消息吗
Any news on Sam?
在那边…来
Um, so somewhere outsi… here.
在密苏里州奥尔德里奇城外
Somewhere outside of Aldrich, Missouri.
小卡正在那里一点点到处找
Cass is going through it with a fine-toothed comb,
我尽可能破解了所有的数据库
and I've cracked every database I could.
什么
Every what?
对了
Right.
你第一次人生中没有互联网
No Internet your first time around.
我们家连电动打字机都没有
Our house didn't have an electric typewriter.
你真的害怕让我承受不来
So…are you really afraid of overwhelming me?
妈妈 我
Mom, look, I am…
很高兴你回来了
thrilled that you're back.
我高兴得要受不了了
I mean, I'm so damn happy, I-I-I can't even stand it.
我就是
I just…
我就是需要点时间来跟上时代
it's just gonna take me a second to catch up, you know?
嗯 当然
Yeah, no, no. Look,
你需要多久都行
take … take all the time you need, all right?
这事就是这样
It's … it is what it is.
等我们找到萨姆
And when we do find Sam…
我要怎么面对他
how am I gonna face him?
什么意思
What do you mean?
黄眼恶魔那晚会去找他 都是因为我
That yellow-eyed thing would never have come for him that night if I…
我引起了这一切
I started all of this.
实在令人惊讶 虽然你和其他猎人
It's just surprising that for all your efforts,
如此努力
yours and all the Hunters,
这国家依然怪物横行
monsters remain rampant in this country.
是啊 我们
Yeah, we just, uh …
只能不断努力了
just keep plugging away, I guess.
你有没有想过 别误会我
Do you ever think … and don't take this the wrong way …
你们中有些人可能有问题
that some of your soldiers may have been compromised?
或是被收买了
Or bought.
我是说
I mean…
没有 我不觉得…
No, I-I don't, um…
一切都好吧
Is everything all right?
不
No!
一切都好吧
Is everything all right?
不
No!
我不该跟你说的
I shouldn't … I shouldn't be talking to you.
你得承认 沉浸其中时还蛮好玩的
You'll have to admit, it was fun while it lasted.
你对我做了什么
What did you do to me?
用药剂和强大的咒语制造了一个幻觉
An hallucination created by potion and powerful spell work.
你觉得爽吗
So…was it good for you?
很遗憾 我不能再重复那个咒语了
Sadly, I can't do the spell again.
你的大脑会化成水 我们不希望那样
Your brain would liquify, which we don't want.
暂时还不
Yet.
所以
So…
我只能采取不那么
I'll have to resort to less…
愉快的办法了
pleasant methods.
强化审讯并不是我工作的一部分
Enhanced interrogation was never part of my job description.
但事实证明
But as it turns out…
我学得很快
…I'm a quick study.
睡得好吗
Hey, how'd you sleep?
做了一整晚的梦
I had dreams all night.
好梦吗
Good dreams?
都是些我已经忘记的东西
Stuff I'd forgotten about.
你爸爸做的很逗的事
Funny stuff your dad did.
他是个好爸爸
He was a great father.
小卡 查到什么了
Hey, Cass, what do you got?
我可能找到萨姆了
I think I may have found Sam's location.
是一间农场
It's a farm.
看上去是空的 但是两周前租了出去
It appears empty, but it was rented two weeks ago.
租给了一个操英国口音的女人
to a woman with an English accent.
你看里面了吗
Did you have a look inside?
没有
No.
那里有很强大的符文保护
No, it's … it's powerfully warded.
很强大的符文
Powerfully warded?
好吧 伙计
Okay, see, buddy, that …
这是大标题啊
that was your headline right there.
我们还在说同一话题吗
Are we still discussing the same thing?
你在哪
Where are you?
我会把地址发给你
I'll text you the address.
好的 我就来
Okay, got it. I'm on my way.
- 我去拿衣服 - 等等
- I'll get my coat. - Wait.
好吧
Okay.
这次我自己去吧
Why don't I take this one solo, okay?
我们并不知道里面的情况
We just … we don't know what we're walking into here.
那是当然的 我们是猎人
We never know. We're Hunters.
好吧
Right.
好吧 我要是担心着你 就不能好好工作
Okay, I-I can't do my job if I'm worried about you.
迪恩
Dean.
你不用担心我
You won't have to be.
我能照顾好自己
I can handle myself.
好吗 好的 谈话愉快
Okay? All right, good talk.
天呐
Oh, boy.
早上好 萨姆 我们重新开始
Good morning, Sam. Let's start again, shall we?
慢慢来
Take our time.
我已经清空了安排
I've cleared my calendar.
我要所有
I would like.
猎人的名字和住址
names and locations of every Hunter…
所有地堡里
the passcodes to each and every.
记录者数据库的密码
Men of Letters database held in the bunker,
还有 对了
and then … oh, yes …
我们谈谈你和恶魔
let's do discuss your relationship.
露比的关系
with the demon Ruby.
米克
Mick.
你真不乖 图妮
You've been a bad girl, Toni.
我来找你了
And I've come to fetch you.
我抓了萨姆·温彻斯特
I have Sam Winchester.
他要松口了 别来打扰我
He's close to breaking. Just leave me be.
不行
No can do.
你违背了命令
You disobeyed orders.
而且 你得知道 你的瓦特女士 死了
Oh, and you should know, your Ms. Watt … quite dead.
迪恩·温彻斯特和他的朋友干的
Courtesy of Dean Winchester and friends.
送我去了最好的寄宿学校
Sent me to the grandest boarding schools,
但我调皮 逃走去追求艺术了
but I was a wee imp and ran away for a life in the arts.
直到我成了明星 我妈妈才肯跟我说话
Mother didn't speak to me until I became a star.
明星
A star?
什么明星
Of?
你有关注皇家芭蕾舞团吗
Uh, do you follow the Royal Ballet?
完全没有
Not a bit.
就是皇家芭蕾舞团
The Royal Ballet.
这让我联想到了我自己的经历
You know, it reminds me a lot of my story.
我也是离开学校去钢厂工作
I left school to work in a steel mill.
一路升职 现在 我是六家钢厂的主人了
I rose up through the ranks, and now I own half a dozen.
不是吧
You're not serious?
再来点酒吗 女士
More wine, madam?
你就像个疖子
You're like a boil that keeps coming back.
我挑掉多少次都会再长出来
no matter how many times I have it lanced.
我猜猜
Let me guess.
你的晚餐男伴多金 单身
Your dinner date is loaded, single,
很可能还有健康问题
and possibly in delicate health.
- 怎么了 - 就是想吐槽一下
- What of it? - Well, just a stab,
但你或许不希望我揭露 他的女伴
but you probably don't want me to reveal that his snookums.
是300岁的老女巫
is 300 years old and a witch.
费格斯 那人把我当女王对待
Fergus, the man treats me like a queen.
这是我抛下
It's my chance to leave behind.
怪物 恶魔和潮湿藏身处的机会
monsters and demons and moldy hideouts.
你敢给我搞砸 我让你兜着走
So help me, if you muck this up.
我可不敢 妈妈
Oh, I wouldn't dream of it, Mummy…
如果你帮我个小忙
if you do me one tiny favor.
帮我对付路西法
Help me with Lucifer.
路西法
Lucifer?
我要算笔账
I have a score to settle.
（文斯·文森特 世界巡演）
为文斯·文森特和
Let's hear it for Vince Vincente.
其他乐队成员鼓掌
and the rest of the band!
下次见 晚安 克利夫兰
See you the next time around. Good night, Cleveland!
我爱你们
I love you guys!
晚安 克利夫兰 我们爱你
Good night, Cleveland! We love you!
文尼 我们今晚去镇上 一起来吧
Hey, Vinny, we're hitting the town tonight. Come with us.
去看看克利夫兰的美景
Check out the wonders of Cleveland.
嗯 不了 谢谢
Yeah, um… I'm good, thanks.
- 汤米 汤米 来啊 - 嗯
- Tommy, Tommy, come on! - Yeah.
回头来找你们
Hey, I'll catch up with you guys later.
哥们
Dude, you …
你得享受你的人生
You got to start living your life, man.
你表演 喝酒 睡觉 表演 喝酒
You perform, you drink, you sleep, perform, drink.
我懂
I-I get it.
我知道
I get it.
听着
Look.
文斯 珍都死了好多年了
Vince, it's been years since Jen died.
我只是想说 哥们
All I mean, brother, is,
她也不会希望你就这么…
don't you think she'd want more for you than just …
出去吧 汤米
Get out of here, Tommy.
去看看克利夫兰
Go see Cleveland.
真不敢相信我听了你的话
I can't believe I let you talk me into this.
我是你妈妈
I'm your mother.
你只能听我的话
You have to do what I say.
听着
Look.
他们直奔了地堡
They targeted the bunker.
显然对你和萨姆非常了解
They obviously know a lot about you and Sam.
他们知道你会去
They'll be expecting you.
但他们绝料不到我
I'm the last person they'd expect.
你原来很厉害 是吧
You were good at this, weren't you?
非常厉害
Very.
问题是 猎人
The thing is, Hunters…
不管多厉害 最终结果都是一样的
no matter how good they are, they all end up the same way.
你死后 爸爸变了
You know when you died, it changed Dad.
他一心要查清真相
I mean, he was Hell-bent on finding out what happened.
猎人的生活占据了他的全部
The Hunter life, it just took him over.
我猜我也是
I guess I was the same.
但萨姆 他不一样
But Sammy … Sammy, he was different.
他想脱离
He wanted out.
他去上了学 去了斯坦福
He went to school. He went to Stanford.
萨姆曾有机会脱离
Sam had a chance to get out?
他却回来了
And he came back?
爸失踪后 萨姆和我去找他
When Dad disappeared, Sam and I looked around,
后来我们明白
and something became very clear.
在这世上 我们唯一拥有的东西
That the only thing we had in this world … the only thing,
除了这辆车
aside from this car …
就是彼此
was each other.
文斯
Vince.
前台
Hello, front desk?
喂
Hello?
文斯
Vince.
不
No.
珍
Jen.
没错 文斯
Yes, Vince.
怎么会
How?
为什么
Why?
我想说对不起
I needed to say I'm sorry.
服下那些药片太自私了
Swallowing those pills was selfish.
这些年我一直想着当初我是怎么对你的
I've had to live all these years knowing how I treated you.
当时 抛下你似乎很公平
At the time, leaving you seemed fair.
因为你曾那么多次抛下我
since you left me so many times.
我只想要你
All I want is you.
这是可以的 文斯
That can happen, Vince.
什么可以
What can happen?
你和我在一起
You and me together.
你是鬼吗
Are you a ghost?
不是
No.
我是天使
I'm an angel.
那是真的
Those are real?
真实而且强大 文斯
Real and very powerful, Vince.
我可以带走你的痛苦
I can take away your pain.
给你安宁
Bring you peace.
你只需要做一件很简单的事
You only have to do one easy thing.
什么事
What?
你愿邀请我进来吗
Will you invite me in?
当然
Yes.
[咒语]
为什么这么慢
What's the bloody hold-up?
电话薄里就他一个撒旦
He's the one and only Satan in the phonebook.
这是巫术 不是谷歌地图
It's witchcraft, not Google Maps.
一般来说 我都有一绺头发
And normally I'd have a piece of hair.
或是一件随身物品来锁定位置
or a belonging to lock on to.
但你连他的样子都不知道
You don't even know what he looks like!
他有股气息
He has an aura.
极致的邪恶
Supreme evil.
锁定那个啊
Lock on to that.
事事都得我来吗
Do I have to do everything?
真不敢相信我又在
I can't believe I'm once again.
一个潮湿的洞里找魔鬼
down some dank hole seeking the devil!
什么时候是个头啊
When does it end?
这就是我退休去了波卡拉顿的原因
It's exactly why I'm retiring to Boca Raton.
跟本一起
With Ben.
本
Ben?
会做很棒的燕麦粥
Who makes oatmeal look fascinating.
他成功 稳定 而且我能比他命长
He's successful, stable, and I'll outlive him.
路西法
Lucifer?
好像是
I think so.
没错 我告诉你地方
Yes. I'll give you the location.
不不 别急
No, no, no. Not now.
我只是想在我们出击前知道
I just want to know who we're dealing with.
我们要对付谁
before we attack.
「我们」是指温家兄弟
By "we, " I presume you mean the Winchesters.
和他们的天使宝宝吧
and their pet angel?
我不需要他们
I don't need them.
你就够了
Just you.
很显然
Look, it's obvious.
我们得把路西法关回笼子里
We got to put Lucifer back in the cage.
而你是唯一做得到的人
You're the only one that can do it.
早该猜到
Should've known.
不行 费格斯
No, Fergus!
我不要再卷入那些破事里了
I'll not be involved in that nonsense again!
或许我该把你的真面目告诉本
Maybe I should tell Ben about you.
或许我该杀了他
Maybe just kill him.
不管怎样 波卡没戏了
Either way, it's bye-bye, Boca.
你个恶毒的蛇
You are a hateful snake.
不管怎样 路西法在皮囊里时
In any case, Lucifer can't be sent back to the cage.
不能被关回笼子
while he's in a vessel.
他不会的
He won't be.
等我们准备好了他就不会了
Not by the time we're ready.
你提到的符文都在哪
Where's all this warding you mentioned?
隐形了
It's cloaked.
非常强大
It's very powerful.
你把你妈也带来了
You brought your mother?
你好 卡西迪奥
Hello, Castiel.
没错
Yes, he did.
你确定里面有人
You sure there's anyone inside?
不确定
No.
中介说租约是远程完成的
The agent said the lease was handled long distance,
但有人给房子加了符文
but someone warded the house.
我去靠近看看
I'm gonna go have a closer look.
妈妈 我行的
Mom, I got this.
你可以不让我开车 迪恩 不能不让我猎魔
You can keep me from driving, Dean. Not from hunting.
我被符文挡在外面了
I'm locked out by the warding.
我需要人陪陪
I could use the company.
谢了
Thanks.
哥们 都中午了 让我进去
Dude, it's noon. Let me in.
瞧瞧你
Look at you.
穿得这么正式去彩排啊
Pretty dressed up for rehearsal, don't you think?
彩排
Rehearsal.
哥们 你没事吧
Brother, are you okay?
嗯 我没法去彩排了
Yeah, I just can't make it to rehearsal.
你有别的事要做吗
Yeah, you got better plans?
是的
I do.
文斯 我说真的
Vince, I'm serious.
我也是
So am I.
好吧
All right.
好了 别闹了
Look, stop screwing around.
我说了 我有事
I said I had plans.
该死
Son of a bitch.
去你妈
Screw yourself.
迪恩
Dean.
我跟你一样很高兴见到他
I'm as happy to see him as you are,
因为 虽然你可以承受
'cause while you may be able to withstand.
我一个个关节地扭断你的身体
my snapping apart your body joint by joint,
你能看着迪恩遭受这折磨吗
can you watch it happen to Dean?
他们告诉我你在这儿
They told me you'd be here.
不是吧
Really?
从我的家具上下来 蹭房的
Get off my furniture, squatter.
路西法
Lucifer.
皮囊是文斯·文森特 二流明星
Wearing Vince Vincente, second-tier star.
我以为比伯更符合你的气质呢
I would've thought Bieber was more your style.
你要么是疯了 要么是傻
You're either mad or dim.
我有个提议
I have a proposal.
你为什么想要统治一帮鱼龙混杂的
I mean, why in Hell would you want to rule over a motley,
白痴恶魔
witless crew of demons?
上帝又去休假了
God's on sabbatical again.
你可以重夺天堂
You could reclaim Heaven.
那块地产才值得统治
Now, that's real estate that's worth ruling.
我可以来掌管分支办事处
I can handle the branch office.
或者
Or…
我可以抬抬手
I could raise my hand,
把你消灭
smite you into oblivion.
[咒语]
有问题吗
Problem?
[咒语]
妈妈的麻痹咒
Mummy's little paralyzing spell.
相信我 很奏效
Trust me, it works.
相信我
Trust me.
不会很久的
Not for long.
圣水
Holy water?
是吗
Yeah?
哎呦
Ooh, ouch.
别无聊了
Don't bore me.
其实 是上等硫酸
Well, actually, it'its top-shelf sulfuric acid.
对你是没有伤害
Harmless to you, I know,
但对你的皮囊 可就伤害大了
but to your vessel, not so much.
密码 萨姆
Passcodes, Sam.
还不说
Not yet?
有什么想补充的吗
Anything to add?
没有 我就是来喝杯茶 挨顿打的
No. No, I just came by for some tea and a beating.
是吗
Really?
我觉得你或许想聊聊你的朋友
See, I thought you might be on for a little chat about your mate,
本杰明·拉菲特
Benjamin Lafitte.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你喊他本尼
You called him Benny.
就是你从炼狱放出来的吸血鬼
You know, the vampire whom you released from Purgatory.
你还跟他成了朋友
and befriended.
这样啊
I see.
好吧
Well…
英国人最有耐心了
the English are nothing if not patient.
好了
Now.
他的灵质 把它送回笼子里
His essence, send it back to the cage.
[咒语]
妈妈
Mother!
[咒语]
不行啊
It's not working.
[咒语]
克劳力不乖哦
Bad, bad Crowley.
不是吧
Seriously?
你把那孩子宠坏了
You spoil that boy.
迪恩
Dean.
我以为你死了
I thought you were dead.
我不确定我还活着
I'm not sure that I'm not.
- 怎么回事 - 我会告诉你的
- So? - I'll tell you.
我会告诉你一切
I'll tell you everything, okay?
首先 生气辣妹是谁
First off, who's Angry Spice?
她是记录者
She, uh … she's … she's Men of Letters.
英国的记录者
Uh, British Men of Letters.
还有那玩意 搞什么
Is that a thing? What the hell?
我们不是一队的吗
Aren't we supposed to be on the same team?
天呐
Oh, God.
先生们 回顾一下
Gentlemen. So, to recap …
你们住在记录者的地堡里
you live in the Men of Letters bunker,
周围是世上最大的神秘知识收藏
awash in the world's greatest collection of occult knowledge,
你们却什么都不知道
and yet you know "Nothing."
没错
Right.
真是浪费
What a waste.
你们两只猿猴似乎没读过一本书
It seems you apes have never read a single book.
记录者一直以智力超群闻名
The Men of Letters has a long tradition of intellectual excellence.
在伦敦 我们对最晦涩的问题
In London, we've undertaken exhaustive studies.
也进行过详尽研究
of even the most arcane topics.
比如 人体痛感最强烈的部位
For example, parts of the body most sensitive to intense pain.
耳鼓膜
The ear drum.
坏牙
Decaying tooth.
腰带下面 不用说了
Below the belt, of course.
还有我最喜欢的 眼皮下面
And my favorite … under the eyelid.
你知道 人是可以疼死的吗
Did you know it's possible to die from pain?
别碰我儿子
Get away from my boys.
妈妈
Mom?
没错
Yeah.
放下
Drop it.
跪地上
Ground.
这才对
That's the ground.
我去
Holy crap.
[咒语]
中止咒语
Kill the spell now.
我不开玩笑
I'm not kidding.
打我 你妈妈就死定了
Shoot me, and your mother has no chance.
枪
The gun.
迪恩
Dean!
没事的
It's okay.
她用的是中国的头脑控制技巧
She was using a Chinese mind-control technique.
一旦失去意识就做不了了
Hard to do when you're unconscious.
看来本猿猴还是读过一两本书的
Turns out this ape did read a book or two.
干得漂亮
Well played.
你们得知的情况大体没错
What yat were told is basically true.
我们很想了解你们俩
We were keen on knowing about the two of you,
因为美国的
seeing as you seem to be.
记录者分部关闭后
partially carrying on the Men of Letters' work here.
你们似乎部分继承了他们的工作
now that the American chapter is defunct.
那你派你的攻击犬是来跟我们打招呼的吗
So you sic your attack dog on us to what, say hi?
我们组织里有些人
Well, part of our group.
怀疑你们美国猎人有渎职行为
suspect some kind of malfeasance amongst you American Hunters.
毫无疑问 贝维尔夫人太过分了
No argument … Lady Bevell went too far.
我深表歉意
I deeply apologize.
她会在伦敦受到惩戒
She'll face consequences in London.
这样吧 你出去走走
I'll tell you what, why don't you take a walk,
让她此时此地就受到惩戒
and she can face those consequences right here and now?
她是我们的人
She's ours.
我们会处理她
We'll take care of her.
我是来递出橄榄枝的
Now, I'm here to extend an olive branch.
我们想跟你们合作
We want to work with you.
我问你个问题 米克吧
Let me ask you a question, uh, Mick is it?
我们为什么要相信你们
Why would we believe any of this?
两位 如果我不是真心
Lads…if I wasn't sincere,
如果我想伤害你们
if I meant you harm,
我有十几种办法可以进来
there's a dozen ways I could've come in here.
劫持你们所有人 而不是赤手空拳地进来
and taken you all prisoner instead of being unarmed.
更别说 我去掉了小屋的符文
Not to mention I powered down all the wardings in this shack.
让你们的攻击犬进得来
so your attack dog could come in.
你可以轻松干掉我 汗都不会流
I reckon you could finish me off without breaking a sweat.
是吧
Am I right?
我从不流汗
I don't sweat under any circumstances.
我的号码
My number.
不着急 冷静下来 好好想想
Take your time, cool down, and just think it over.
你们怕失去什么呢 除了你们最糟的噩梦
And what have you got to lose, except your worst nightmares?
太好吃了 谢谢 妈妈
Oh, that was fantastic. Thank you, Mom.
我就是点了外卖菜单上的几道菜
All I did was point at some stuff on a take-out menu.
我本想做饭 但我不会
I would've cooked, but I, uh…don't.
等等
Well, now, wait.
你的肉卷很好吃啊
Your meat loaf was amazing.
小猪扭扭买来的
Came from the Piggly Wiggly.
抱歉打破你的幻想了
Sorry to burst your bubble.
你还喜欢派吗
But do you still like pie?
我…
I mean…
萨姆
Sam.
你总看着我 好像我要爆炸似的
You keep looking at me like I'm going to explode.
对不起
I'm sorry.
怎么样
But what do we think?
要相信英国佬那套「我们做朋友吧」的话吗
Are we buying that Brit's whole "let's be friends" routine?
- 不可能 - 不信
- No. No way. - No.
你还能吃得更快点吗
Could you eat that any faster?
不能
No. No, I cannot.
我们该打给互联网
Well, we should call the Internet.
尽量了解一下这些人的情况
and find out as much as we can about these people.
我说对了吗
Did I say that right?
很接近了
So close.
嗯 接近了
Yeah, it was close.
你来点吗
You want any?
暂时不用
No. Uh, not now.
我得说 罗威娜
You know, I got to say, Rowena,
我一看你
I took one look at you,
就想再折断一次你讨厌的脖子
and all I wanted was to snap your miserable neck again.
这次让你恢复不过来
And keep it snapped this time.
但我决定不那么做
But I think I've decided against it.
你不会后悔的 先生
You won't regret it, sir.
我不再搅和这些事了
I'm done with all this.
我会躲得远远的
I'll stay far, far away,
去我的网球俱乐部里跟共和党人一起喝马丁尼
sipping martinis with republicans at my tennis club.
你没懂
You're missing my point.
你这样天资聪明的女巫
A witch as gifted as yourself,
此外 还有《诅咒之书》
with access to the Book of the Damned to boot,
作为囚徒对我更有价值
would be much more valuable as a prisoner.
什么
What?
那句话怎么说的
How's that saying go?
朋友要亲近
Mm, friends close…
敌人要更近
…enemies closer.
不
No.
不要
No!
什么事
Yes?
抱歉 希望没吵醒你
Sorry. I hope I didn't wake you up.
我想给你端这个
I-I, uh…wanted to bring you this.
- 谢谢 - 不客气
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
我不知道你喝不喝茶
I don't know if you drink tea, but…
- 我喝 - 很好
- I do. - Good.
我想说
Uh, and I wanted to say…
如果你想谈谈
if you ever want to talk,
我理解回到人间
I know what it's like to come back.
觉得自己格格不入的感觉
and not feel like you really fit.
我要补上好多关于你们的事
I just have so much about you boys to catch up on.
妈妈的事
Mother stuff.
第一颗牙 第一次暗恋
You know, first tooth, first crush.
是啊
Yeah.
我有好多空白要填补
I just have a lot of blanks to fill in.
好
Right, uh…
爸爸的日记
Dad's journal.
他自己写的
His writing, his words.
让我填补了不少空白
Helped me fill in some blanks,
回答了一些我原本没想到过的问题
answer some questions I didn't know I had.
也算是让他
And, you know, it … it … it.
继续留在我们身边了
keeps him with us, sort of.
谢谢
Thank you.
晚安
Good night.
迪恩说你脱离了猎魔
Dean said you got out of hunting.
是啊
Yeah.
但你又回来了
And yet here you are.
这是我的家庭
Well, this is my family.
我们家猎魔 我们就做这个
My family hunts, you know? It's what we do.
妈妈
Mom.
对于我
For me…
光是
just, um…
你在这儿
having you here…
就填补了最大的空白
fills in the biggest blank.
（来复枪专家）
我不会上飞机的
I will not get on that plane.
你会的
Yes, you will.
你的任务是找到美国猎人
Your mission was to identify American Hunters.
取得他们的信任
and gain their trust.
那是总部的要求
That's what the home office wants.
是礼 不是兵
Honey, not vinegar.
我有份案卷 我这才刚开始
I have a dossier, and I am just getting started.
他们也做成了不少事
They've also had their fair share of successes.
如果我们的目标是终结这里的超自然威胁
If our goal is to end the supernatural threat here,
我们得摧毁一切障碍
we need to destroy every obstacle.
温家兄弟 这些美国猎人
The Winchesters, these American Hunters,
他们不比他们控制不了的
they're no better than the monsters.
那些怪物强到哪去
they fail to control.
他们该被铲除
They need to be eliminated.
米克
Mick.
如果走到那一步 夫人
If push comes to shove, your ladyship,
我做好了那个准备
I'm prepared for that.
你会下狠手吗
You'll get your hands dirty?
那种事可以留给凯奇先生
Well, we have Mr. Ketch for that.
你会叫他来
You'll send for him?
我已经叫了
I already have.